<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Personal Diary</string>
    <string name="add">+</string>
    <string name="Date">Date</string>
    <string name="Add">Add</string>
    <string name="Diary_Entry">Diary Entry</string>
    <string name="entry1_date">25th May,2022</string>
    <string name="entry2_date">26th May,2022</string>
    <string name="entry3_date">27th May,2022</string>
    <string name="entry4_date">28th May,2022</string>
    <string name="entry5_date">29th May,2022</string>
    <string name="entry1_content">Today was my first day at school. Since we recently shifted to this city, everything here is new to me. It is a little difficult and often frustrating to get adjusted to everything, especially the people. For the most part, the day was uneventful, except for me being asked to introduce myself over and over again by every teacher that came. I made a few new friends too. I am sure I’ll have great fun. I have already begun to like this place.</string>
    <string name="entry2_content">I woke up at 6 oclock in the morning. We had breakfast and dressed up. Today we all went to Fantasize Amusement park near Pune. We started from home at 7 oclock. As soon as we reached there, we bought our tickets and went inside. I was so excited seeing the rides. My parents and brother liked the Thunderfall ride. My favorite rides were Water Splash, Caterpillar Ride, Wave Pool and Pirate Ship. After a couple of hours, we had our lunch. In the afternoon we had the scariest ride that is the Space Gun. We got back to our home in the evening. It was a great day and I enjoyed a lot. </string>
    <string name="entry3_content">I am very sorry for not writing to you last night. I was extremely tired after enjoying the entire day at Shangrila Resort. I could not even keep my eyes open. The place was so huge that by the end of the day we still felt like we did not see the entire place. It had one large pool for adults, two pools for children over 10 years, and a really shallow yet very cute pool for small children. There was a large waterfall as well. The entire place was surrounded by grass and trees. It felt as if we were in a real jungle. They also had speakers hidden in the trees giving sound effects of wild animals. The food too was fresh and filling. It gave us the energy to go on playing. We had a great time and wished we could stay there forever.</string>
    <string name="entry4_content">Last night, I had a very strange dream. I saw that two of my friends and I were going to attend my cousin’s wedding reception. On our way a rather strange-looking man intercepted us. Despite our protests, he insisted on narrating to us his tale of resentment. He looked unnaturally old with skinny limbs and glittering eyes, and the tale he narrated seemed too surreal to be true. He said he used to be a mariner who shot an innocent albatross who was guiding their ship out of the perilous ice at sea. This act enraged a powerful spirit who used to love the bird. His actions resulted in the death of his crewmates. Also, he was doomed to feel a great deal of agony which was relieved only when he narrated the tale to somebody. The dream taught me a valuable lesson: Never hurt the hand which helps you.</string>
    <string name="entry5_content">Tomorrow is the judgment day as they call it—the elocution competition that I have been preparing for all these days. I will be participating in it tomorrow. Just the thought of it has me shaken. My class teacher knows my insecurities about speaking to crowds. Maybe that’s why she forced me to take this up. I wonder what will happen tomorrow. I have prepared a fairly good speech with my elder brother’s help. I’ve already practiced it so many times that I can recite it in my sleep. I have to go to sleep now or else I will be late for school.</string>
</resources>